First of all, I've had extensive conversations
with the Prime Minister of Israel
over the last several days, almost an hour each.
And I've made the case, and I feel very strongly about it,
that there has to be a temporary ceasefire
to get the prisoners out, to get the hostages out.
And that is underway.
I'm still hopeful that that can be done.
And in the meantime, I don't anticipate,
I'm hoping that the Israelis will not make
any massive land invasion in the meantime.
So it's my expectation that's not going to happen.
There has to be a ceasefire temporarily to get those hostages.
By the way, there are — we're in a situation
where there are American hostages.
American citizens are being held hostage.
It's not just — not just Israelis.
It's American hostages as well.
And, you know, my hope and expectation
is that we'll get this hostage deal.
We'll bring the Americans home.
And the deal is being negotiated now.
And we're going to see where it takes us.